<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Agile]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Agile]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/agile/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 15:40:42 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/agile/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>TECHNOLOGY  We help our customers make appropriate technology choices en route to solutioning for the problems at hand. The elegance of our technology solutions is rooted in our understanding of the implications of different technology choices combined with the passion for engineering excellence and the zeal to constantly push ourselves towards the cutting edge of technology.    DELIVERY  We pride ourselves in delivering simple solutions to complex business needs. Be it fulfilling the digital strategy incorporating cloud, mobile & social across devices and platforms, or building and evolving custom products, or providing big and unstructured data analytics, our strong delivery capability helps us partner with our customers in realising their business goals.    CONSULTING  From designing the User Experience for greenfield applications, to introducing Lean & Agile methodologies in organisations and incorporating Continuous Delivery strategies across complex technology environments, our customers trust us not only for our expertise in recommending strategies, but also for our ability to work alongside them in jointly delivering business value.    ENABLEMENT  We enable technology organizations raise their performance levels and become strong and reliable business enablers. Our offerings focus on simplifying existing software development processes through process optimisation, creating approaches for evolving technology architecture, coaching and handholding through implementation of Lean & Agile practices.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/agile/technology-we-help-our-customers-make-appropriate-technolog/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">12f8424f-f88f-4d9e-aaf5-f3049a89c25d</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 15:40:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sahaj Software Solutions]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Sahaj Software Solutions</h1><p>The word Sahaj has its origins in the Sanskrit language and it represents simplicity. Our endeavour is to deliver outcomes which embrace aspects of simplicity represented by elegance, clarity and sophistication. We believe that this cannot happen without a strong commitment to understanding our customer's problems, a solution mindset and a commitment towards engineering excellence.</p><img src="http://sahajsoft.com/images/sahaj-meaning.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://sahajsoft.com/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">36d33838-c744-422b-aaae-364092e6ba35</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2015 15:37:30 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>